Something Evil is a tv movie, horror film directed by Steven Spielberg.
A young couple moves into a farmhouse in rural Pennsylvania.
What they don't know is that there is an unseen presence in the
house, and that it wants to take possession of the wife.
Marjorie Worden, played by Sandy Dennis.
Paul Worden, played by Darren McGavin.
Harry Lincoln, played by Ralph Bellamy.
Gehrmann, played by Jeff Corey.
Stevie Worden, played by Johnny Whitaker.
Ernest Lincoln, played by John Rubinstein.
Something Evil is a 1972 American TV movie starring Sandy
Dennis, Darren McGavin and Ralph Bellamy.
Directed by Steven Spielberg, the screenplay was written by Robert Clouse.
The film explores themes of pennsylvania, usa,
supernatural, possession, isolated farmhouse.
The tone is dark.